听力考试正式开始。请看听力部分第一节。第一节，听下。面五个句子，从每小题所给的
B, I like apples very much.
三幅图中选出与句子内容相关的选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。听完每个句子后，你都有五秒钟的时间作答和阅读下一小题。每个句子读两遍。现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读第一小题的有关内容。
2. The horse is running fast.
The horse is running fast.
3. There is a clock on the
is a clock on the wall.
4. Please turn right at the first crossing.
Please turn turn right at the first crossing.
5. The girl was watering flowers when we saw her.
The girl was watering flowers when we saw her.
第一节到此结束。第二节。听下面七段对话，从每小题所给的
,B Hello, this is Sunshine Hotel.
三个选项中选出正确答案，并标在试卷的相应位置。听完每段对话后，你都有五秒钟的时间回答有关小题，和五秒钟的时间阅读下一小。题。每段对话读两遍。听第一段对话，回答第六小题。现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读这一小题
听第二段对话，回答第七小题。现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读这一小题
听第三段对话，回答第八小题。现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读这一小题。
听第四段对话，回答第九小题。现在。你有五秒钟的时间阅读这一小题。
听第五段对话，回答第十和十一题两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
听第六段对话，回答第十二和十三题两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
听第七段对话，回答第十四和十五题两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个。小题。
第二节到此结束。第三节，听下面的对话，根据你所听到的内容完成以下表格，每空填一词。听对话前，你将有二十秒钟的时间阅读表格内容。对话读三。变。
Can I help you?
Yes, I'd like to rooms.
Could you please tell me when you will arrive?
On March 7th.
And I'll stay there for three days.
How many rooms would you like?
Four single rooms.
How much are they?
300 yuan for one single room a night.
Alright. What services come with that?
You'll have a TV, a telephone, and some English newspapers.
And you'll also get a free breakfast.
Could I have the rooms which face south?
Of course. Four single rooms which face south from March 7th to 9th.
Am I right?
Exactly. Could you tell me your name, please?
Smith. What's your telephone number?
398 -2845. Got it.
Hope to see you at our hotel.
Hello, this is Sunshine Hotel.
Can I help you?
Yes, I'd like to book rooms.
Could you please tell me when you will arrive?
On March 7th.
And I'll stay there for three days.
How many rooms would you like?
Four single rooms.
How much are they?
300 yuan for one single room a night.
Alright. What services come with that?
You'll have a TV, a telephone, and some English newspapers.
And you'll also get a free breakfast.
Could I have the rooms which face south?
Of course. Four single rooms which face south from March 7th to 9th.
Am I right?
Exactly. Could you tell me your name, please?
Wendy Smith. What's your telephone number?
398 -2845. Got it.
Hope to see you at our hotel.
Hello, this is Sunshine Hotel.
Can I help you?
Yes, I'd like to book rooms.
Could you please tell me when you will arrive?
On March 7th.
And I'll stay there for three days.
How many rooms would you like?
single rooms. How much are they?
300 yuan for one single room a night.
Alright. What services come with that?
You'll have a TV, a telephone, and some English newspapers.
And you'll also get a free breakfast.
Could I have the rooms which face south?
Of course. Four single rooms which face south from March 7th to 9th.
Am I right?
Exactly. Could you tell me your name, please?
Wendy Smith. What's your telephone number?
398 -2845. Got it.
Hope to see you at our hotel.
第三节到此结束。现在你有两分钟的时间将试卷上的答案填涂到答题卡上。
Thank you for watching.
听力部分到此结束。
watching.